Guide to the Jerome T. Barrett Collection, 1913-2010 LAC0007
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Jerome T. Barrett Papers, 1937-2005; Record Group 2
  - Mediation Research and Studies, 1950-2009; Record Group 2 Series 6
    - Public Opinion Quarterly-"Processes of Opinion change" by Herbert C. Kelman, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 7)
    - Miscellanous Notes, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 8)
    - Reprint: "Training the Mediator" by Harold Davis, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 9)
    - University of Michigin Medical Center slides-"Mutual Gains & Collaborative Bargaining in Today's Health Care Settings", undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 10)
    - Labor Law Journal-"A Technique to Improve Industrial Relations" & "Government Intervention in Labor Disputes", 1950-1954; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 11)
    - Journal of Applied Psychology (Vol.42, No.5)-"Guttman-Typee Scales for Union and Management Attitudes" with attached note, October, 1958; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 12)
    - Reprint: Personnel Journal-"Strategy vs. Tactics in Bargaining" by B.J Speroff, January, 1962; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 13)
    - Reprint: "Public Policy and Emergency Disputes" by Cyrus Smythe -Labor Law Journal, University of Minnesota, October, 1963; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 14)
    - Notes and Reprint: "Student Perceptions of Causes of Labor-Management Conflict" by John Lloyd, University of Iowa Monograph Series 10, May, 1968; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 15)
    - Reprint: "Mediation: a path to campus peace? by Sam Zagoria, January 1969; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 16)
    - "Foundations of Collective Bargaining" course syllabus, 1974; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 17)
    - "Public-Worker Strike Acceptance growing" from American Teacher, Vol.59, No.5, January, 1975; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 18)
    - Public-Personnel Management-From Conflict to Cooperation" by Michael Garvey & George E. O'Connell, September-October, 1976; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 19)
    - Labor Studies Journal (Vol 4, No.2)-"Meidation Techniques in Four Countries" by Amira Galin & Joseph Krislov, 1979; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 20)
    - Revised draft: "A New Way to Settle Grievances in the Forest Products Industry"-FPMA, 1979; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 21)
    - Reprint: "Collective Bargaining and the Theory of Conflict" by Jack Barbush, March, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 22)
    - Bureau of National Affairs-Federal Notes, June, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 23)
    - Richard Leone correspondence-FMCS article, March, 1981; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 24)
    - Newsclip: Wall Street Journal-"More Firms Turn to Privacy courts to Avoid Expensive Legal Fights", January, 1984; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 25)
    - The Conservation Foundation-"Resolving Environmental Disputes" by Gail Bingham, 1985; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 26)
    - Massachusetts District Court Mediation Project-"Community Mediation: Progress and Problems" by George Nicolau, August, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 27)
    - Newsclipping:"Labor Loses the Strike as a Weapon"-The Washington Post, 1992; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 28)
    - Resolutions newsletter, Vol 1, No.1, Summer 1992; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 29)
    - Summary: "Labor Relations at New York Daily News" by Kenneth M. Jennings, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 30)
    - Draft: "Dispute Resolution in Peru: Past, Present, and Future Challenges" by Ivan Ormachea-Choque, JD, July 1995; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 31)
    - The Recorder-"Credibility is Everything" by Cliff Paletsky, November 20, 1996; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 32)
    - The Futurist-"Collective Bargaining for the Future" by Cynthia Burton and Edward Cohen-Rosenthal, March-April, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 33)
    - FMCs Annual Report Timeline-Printout, April 2001; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 189, Folder 34)
    - University of Minnesota-"Scholarship Notes & Reprint: "A Look at Labor Education in Germany", June 12-July 5, 1961; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - IBN Transparencies for Win-Win & Briefing -Part 1, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - IBN Transparencies for Win-Win & Briefing -Part 2, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - "The Abrasive Personality" by Harry Levison, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - American Bar Association pamphlet-"Build Your Practice with this New Video", undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Article: "Labor's Peacemaker" by Jay Goldman, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - "A Chronological History of Labour Canada: the Major Milestones" by Vincent C. Rigby, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Dickinson Law Review-"Pennsylvania Labor Relations Board" by James L Cowden, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - FMCS Orientation Seminar-"Interest Based Bargaining" by George Buckingham Jr., undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Georgia State University-"The Functional Role of Labor-Management Committees" by John Schmidman, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Harper's Magazine-"Law's wont stop strikes" by Donald Strauss, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Harvard Law School-Price Information/Order form for Clearinghouse Teaching Materials, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Industrial Relations-"Behavioral Studies of third Intervention" by Janette Webb, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations Review-"Communications: The Theory of Bargaining", undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - "Mediation of Labor Disputes: Art, Science, or Misterie?", undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Mediation Procedures and Techniques, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Miscellanous Notes- Photocopy, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Outlines of Theory of Grievances, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Packet-"Reducing Incidence of Strikes Prior to Active Mediation", undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Purdue & University of Minnesota-"An Empirical Assessment of a Theory of Interest Arbitrator Behavior" by Mario Bognanno and James Dworkin, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 17)
    - Reprint: "A Sparrow who got caught in a Badminton Game" by Saul Wallen (Air Line Pilots' Magazine), undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 18)
    - University of Minnesota-:Needed Research on the Mediation of Labor Disputes" by Arnold Rose, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 19)
    - FDR Presidential Papers-"Executive Order No.6511-Power of the National Labor Board", December 16, 1933; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 20)
    - Public Law 101-80th Congress: "text of Labor Management Relations Act", 1947; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 21)
    - "Economics of Labor and Industrial Relations" -Pages 632 to 637; by Gordon Bloom & Herbert Northrup, 1950; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 22)
    - Journal of Industrial and Labor Relations-"Mediation or Meddling" by Allan Weisenfeld, January 1954; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 23)
    - D.G. Dayton-General Electric Speeches, Feb.-July 1954; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 24)
    - Excerpt: "Beating Labor Trouble to the Draw" from Business Weekly, October 30, 1954; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 25)
    - Personnel Psychology-"A Clinical Psychologist's Treatment of Labor-Management Conflicts" by George Muench, 1958; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 26)
    - Labor Law Journal articles, 1958-1979; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 27)
    - Ohio State University-Thesis: Mediation of Labor Disputes" by David B. McCalmont, 1961; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 28)
    - Industrial and Labor Relations Review-"The Semi-Strike" by David B. McCalmont, January 1962; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 29)
    - Science, Vol. 145, No. 3628-"Economics and the Quality of Life" by John Kenneth Galbraith, July 10, 1964; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 30)
    - Training Directors Journal Vol. 18-"Contract Negotiations: A Laboratory Approach" by Floyd Brandt & Charles Klasson, Dec. 1964; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 31)
    - AFL-CIO American Federationist-"Why Strike? Facts vs. Fiction", November, 1965; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 32)
    - Negro Digest: "Collective Bargaining: the Civil Rights Progress" by Albert A. Blum, Nov. 1965; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 33)
    - Personnel Journel Vol.44-"Crisis Bargaining" by Edward Peters, 1965; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 34)
    - Indianapolis Star & Wall Street News Clips, 1965-1967; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 35)
    - University of Alabama Thesis-"The Natural History and Purpose of Mediation" by Jack E Steen, 1965; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 36)
    - Settling Disputes in the Community Course-syllabus, 1968; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 37)
    - Personnel-"Collective Bargaining: A Union;s Program for Reducing Conflict" by Irving Stern and Robert Pearse, May-June, 1968; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 38)
    - Training and Development Journal, Vol.23, No.1-"How Labor and Management View Preventive Mediation Training" by Harold White & Robert Dyer, January, 1969; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 39)
    - George Washington Law Review, Vol.37, No.4-"Resolution of Social Conflict through Collective Bargaining" by Bernard Indik & Georgina Smith, May 1969; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 40)
    - John Mead and Joseph Krislov articles, 1969-1972; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 198, Folder 41)
    - Engineering Employers's Federation-"Greener Grass"" by J.P. Lowry, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 1)
    - Draft: Proposal for a Course in Community Dispute Settlement, Feb. 9, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 2)
    - Executive Order 11491: Labor-Management Relations in the Federal Service, August 26, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 3)
    - Association of Labor Mediation Agencies-"Labor Mediation: An Exploratory Survey" Kenneth Kressel, 1971-1977; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 4)
    - "Future Possibilities in Collective Bargaining" by Donna J. Lucas, March, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 5)
    - Hawaii Employers Council-Industrial Relations Digest, July, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 6)
    - Washington University-"The Social Science Institute: "Third Party Intervention in Community Conflict" by James Lane & Gerald Cormick, Sept. 18-19, 1973; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 7)
    - Notes and Draft Questionaires: Mediation Research and Project, with George Buckingham, 1976; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 8)
    - American Arbitration Association-"State of the Art of Dispute Resolution Training" conference, June 9-10, 1977; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 9)
    - Cornell University-"A Theory and Empirical Examination of the Public Sector Mediation Process" by Thomas Kochan and Todd Jick, June 1977; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - FMCS National Seminar-"Sources of Conflict and Conflict Resoltuion Strategies", November 9, 1977; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Labor History-"The Organization of Work in the Men's Clothing Industry" by Daniel Walkowitz, June 1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Federal Labor-Management Consultant 1 FMLC 78-21, October 20, 1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - JEIT 2, 6-"Should We Do Some Joint Training?" by Peter Smith and Malcom Leary, 1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - FMCS Seminar Syllabus-"Mediation Methods and Techniques"-Republic of the Philippines, 1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Christopher Honeyman Articles, 1978-1990; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Cornell University-Mediation Research Questionnaire & Correspondence, December, 1979; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - WWR-"New Work Patterns Suited to Changing Relationshop between Work, Home Life", April, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 18)
    - "Conflict Resolution: Prospects for the Future" by John R Coleman, December, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 19)
    - Psychological Bulletin Vol.87, No.2-"Experimental Research on Third-Party Intervention" by Jeffrey Z. Rubin, 1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 20)
    - Resolve: Center for Environmental Conflict Resolution-newsletter, 1980-1981; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 21)
    - Labor Law Journal-"Grievance Mediation" by Mollie Bowers & "A Discussion" by Laverne Rolle Alian, August 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 22)
    - Remarks: Secretary of Labor Raymond Donovan-National Labor-Management conferece, August, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 23)
    - Workplace Democracy Vol.9, No,.4-"Focus on Labor", 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 24)
    - Human Resource Management-"Using Labor/Management Committees to Improve Productivity" by Paul J. Champagne, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 199, Folder 25)
    - Atlantic Monthly-"The Next American Frontier," by Robert Reich, March, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Kroger Company-Nashville Distribution Center correspondence, August, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - University of Hawaii at Manoa Occasional Paper No.146-"Professional Updating of Personnel" by Charles M. Rehmus, August, 1983; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - University of Illinois Third-Party Survey, July 13, 1984; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Monthly Labor Review, Vol.107, No.11-"BLS and the Economy: a Centennial Timetable" by Edgar Weinberg, Nov. 1984; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Photocopy:" When Health Care Employees Strike4"-Chapter 1" by Norman Metzger, Joseph Ferentino, and Kenneth Kruger, Nov. 1984; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - The Arbitration Journal-"Resolving Unjust Discharge Cases" by Leonard Bierman & Stuart Youngblood, March, 1985; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Harvard University-John Donlup Correspondence, April 1, 1985; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Psychology Today-"Why Negotiationgs Go Wrong" by Max H. Bazerman, June, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 9)
    - Monthly Labor Review-"Trends in Health Services Employment" by Anne Kahl & Donald Clark, August, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 10)
    - AA News-"Study of Mediators Says Men, Women differ in Priorities, not in results", December 1, 1986; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 11)
    - Oregon School Study Council. Vol, 31, No.1-"Collaborative Bargaining in Schools" by Demetri Liontos, Sept, 1987; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Japan Institute of Negotiation: "One Way Ahead" by Larry Crump, Dec. 6, 1988; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 13)
    - University of California-"Generative Learning and Role Playing in Teaching Conflict Resolution" by David R. Stiebel, 1988; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 14)
    - Negotiation Journal-"Grievance Mediation and Other Alternatives to Arbitration" by Stephen Goldberg, 1989; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 15)
    - Pennsylvania Bureau of Mediation-"Timed Mediation Process: A Forty-Eight Hour Formula to Success" by Harris Woffard and Thomas J. Quinn, 1990; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 16)
    - Deborah Kolb Articles, 1991-1995; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 17)
    - NEA Research Division-"Collaborative Bargaining: A Critical Appraisal", 1991; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 18)
    - Negotiation Journal-"Response to Feuille Paper" by Rolf Valtin, April, 1992; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 19)
    - Institute for Conflict Analysis and Resolution Occasional Paper 6: "Peacemaking and Conflict Resolution" by Hon. Samuel W. Lewis, April, 1993; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 20)
    - Cornell University-"Institute of Collective Bargaining: "Strategic Bargaining and Information Exchange" by Michael H. Belzer, Sept. 1993; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 21)
    - Institute for Multi-Track Diplomacy, Occasional Paper No. 4-"Beyond Win/Win" by Louise Diamond, November 1994; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 22)
    - Summary of Final Report of Dunlop Commission, January, 1995; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 23)
    - Virginia Mediation Network workshop-"Transformative Mediation in Theory and Practice" by Robert A Baruch Bush-Sheraton Reston Hotel, May 11, 1995; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 24)
    - Dispute Resolution Journal-American Arbitration Association, 1995-1997; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 25)
    - MIT Sloan School of Management-Interview Correspondence, 1995; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 26)
    - Public Lawer-"What Every Lawyer Should about Government ADR", 1997; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 27)
    - National Institute for Trial Advocacy Pamphlet-"Mediation Advocacy" by John W. Cooley, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 28)
    - IRC Press-"The Changing role of the Neutral in Dispute Resolution" by George Adams, 1997; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 29)
    - Review of Public Personnel Administration-Vol. xviii, No.4, 1998; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 30)
    - Rutgers University-Patricia Mareschal correspondence and research materials, 2000-2002; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 31)
    - Theodore W. Kheel-Interview and Correspondence materials, 2001; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 32)
    - The Chronicle-National Academy of Arbitrators, 2009; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 200, Folder 33)
    - "Personal & Professional- The Art of Lecturing:A Few Simple Ideas Can Help Teachers Improve Thier Skills" newsclip, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 11)
    - Teaching Transparencies-Part 1, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 12)
    - Teaching Transparencies-Part 2, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 13)
    - Business Week, No.930-"A New Deal for America's Employers", June 28, 1947; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 14)
    - National Center for Productivity and Quality of Working Life-"Thid Party" conference Agenda and Information Packet, August-September 1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 15)
    - Labor Studies Journal, Vol.6, No.3-"Steward Performance: A Behaviorally Anchored Description" by Hoyt Wheeler and Anthony DeAngelis, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 16)
    - Senior Executive Association/Profession Development League-"SES today and Tomorrow" Seminar Agenda, April 24, 1982; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 209, Folder 17)
    - Cornell University-"The Use of ADR in U.S. Corporations" by David Lipsky and Ronald L. Seeber, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Miscellanous Notes-Collective Bargaining & "Marketing Materials" Floppy Disk, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Penn State University Labor Education Department-Class Material Packet, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 3)
    - University of Iowa-"Collective Negotiations and Public Administration" by Harold Davey, undated; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 4)
    - Cornell University Industrial and Labor Relations Library-Reference Memorandum #1, December 1967; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 5)
    - Union Merger Newsclips-Misc., 1968-1978; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - The Brookings Institute Reprints: 167, 179 & 185, 1969-1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 7)
    - Harbridge House Inc.-Morris Sackman Materials and Correspondence, Summer 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 8)
    - Reprint: Industrial Relations Journal, "The Literature of Labour Economics and Industrial Relations: A Guide to its Source" by George Sayars Bain and Gillian B. Woolven, Summer 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 9)
    - NYS PERS Grant Application-"Master's Degree for Training of Neutrals" Project, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 10)
    - The Twentieth Century Fund/New York-"Pickets at City Hall" Report, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 11)
    - Reprint: Industrial and Labor Relations Review, Vol. 22, No.3-"The Structure and Scope of Appeals Procedures for Public Employees" by Joseph Ullman and James Begin, April, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 12)
    - National Federation of Federal Employees Biannual conference-"The Agreement Making Process in Public Disputes" by Robert J. Callaway, September 15, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 13)
    - FMCS Nashville-" New Concepts in Public Sector Collective Bargaining" by William Kilberg, September 23, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 14)
    - University of Arizona, Tucson-"Recommendations and Suggested Legislative Framework for Public Employment Relations" by James C. McBrearty, November, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 15)
    - Council of State Governments-"State-Local Employee Labor Relations", December, 1970; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 16)
    - Industrial Relations Research Association, New York Chapter-Chairman Arvid Anderson Addresses, April 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 17)
    - PPA Central Regional conference-"Job Restructuring and Position Classification" Notes and correspondence, April, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 18)
    - Conference on New Directions in Collective Bargaining-"Negotiation in the Public Sector" by Kenneth E. Moffet, April 28, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 19)
    - Federal Bar Association-Secretary J.D. Hodgson Remarks and Press Releases, April 29, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 20)
    - National Association of Government Employees conference-Robert Callaway Remarks, October 1, 1971; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 21)
    - Reprint: Wisconsin Law Review-Vol.1973, No.4-"The Impact of Public Sector Bargaining" by Arvid Anderson, 1974; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 22)
    - "Position Paper on the FMCS Involvement in non-Federal Public Sector Disputes"-Fishgold, 1974; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 23)
    - NEA News Service-Faye Ford Remarks & Gilbert E. Donahue Remarks, " A Federal Perspective on Teacher Labor Relations", May 1974-February 1975; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 24)
    - Public Sector Impasse Speeches-Kenneth E. Moffett and Jacob Seidenberg Remarks, April-May, 1974; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 25)
    - Alama C. Filley booklet-"Small Group Dynamics-Or Why the Negotiation Team Acts that way.", 1976; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 228, Folder 26)
    - Miscellanous ADR Publications, 1976-2003; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - NYS PERS correspondence, 1976-1980; Record Group 2 Series 6 (Box 229, Folder 2)